<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AlfaSenior</string>
    <string name="safety_intro">In this module, you will learn how to identify scams via SMS and phone calls. We will teach best practices to avoid falling for banking and identity fraud.</string>
    <string name="first_step_safety">1. Never click on suspicious links sent via SMS or email.</string>
    <string name="second_step_safety">2. Always verify the source of the number before answering unknown calls.</string>
    <string name="third_step_safety">3. Banks never ask for full passwords over the phone or via messages.</string>
    <string name="fourth_step_safety">4. If you receive a money request from a family member, confirm directly with them before transferring.</string>
    <string name="fifth_step_safety">5. If in doubt, ask a family member for help or call the bank\'s official support.</string>
    <string name="security">Security</string>
    <string name="module_security">Module: Security</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="welcome_alfasenior">Welcome to AlfaSenior!</string>
    <string name="learn_whatsapp">Learn WhatsApp</string>
    <string name="learn_phone">Learn Phone</string>
    <string name="learn_internet">Learn Internet</string>
    <string name="learn_safety">Learn Security</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="module_whatsapp">Module: WhatsApp</string>
    <string name="whatsapp">WhatsApp</string>
    <string name="intro_whatsapp">In this module, you will learn how to send messages, voice notes, and make video calls on WhatsApp.</string>
    <string name="first_step_whatsapp">1. To send a message, tap the chat icon and select a contact.</string>
    <string name="second_step_whatsapp">2. Type your message and tap the send button (right arrow).</string>
    <string name="third_step_whatsapp">3. To send a voice note, press and hold the microphone icon and speak.</string>
    <string name="fourth_step_whatsapp">4. To make a video call, open the contact\'s chat and tap the camera icon.</string>
    <string name="fifth_step_whatsapp">5. Never share passwords or security codes via WhatsApp!</string>
    <string name="intro_phone">In this module, you will learn how to make calls, answer calls, and save contacts.</string>
    <string name="first_step_phone">1. To make a call, open the phone app and dial the desired number.</string>
    <string name="second_step_phone">2. Tap the call button (phone icon) to start the call.</string>
    <string name="third_step_phone">3. To answer a call, swipe the green button up.</string>
    <string name="fourth_step_phone">4. To save a contact, tap "Add Contact" after the call.</string>
    <string name="fifth_step_phone">5. You can block unknown numbers in the phone app settings.</string>
    <string name="cellphone">Phone</string>
    <string name="module_cellphone">Module: Phone</string>
    <string name="intro_internet">In this module, you will learn how to browse the internet, search for information, and access websites safely.</string>
    <string name="first_step_internet">1. To access the internet, open your phone’s browser, such as Chrome or Firefox.</string>
    <string name="second_step_internet">2. In the search bar, type what you want to look for and tap "Search."</string>
    <string name="third_step_internet">3. Always check if a website starts with "https://" before entering personal information.</string>
    <string name="fourth_step_internet">4. Avoid clicking on suspicious ads that appear on websites and social media.</string>
    <string name="fifth_step_internet">5. For better security, always keep your browser and apps updated.</string>
    <string name="internet">Internet</string>
    <string name="module_internet">Module: Internet</string>
    <string name="listen">Listen</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="modo_alto_contraste">High Contrast Mode</string>
</resources>
